[{"answer": " I am really excited for you.  Planning a wedding is going to be so much fun", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 11, "question": "", "qSentId": 10},{"answer": " I know.  I am so excited.  I cant believe its actually happening", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 12, "question": " I am really excited for you.  Planning a wedding is going to be so much fun", "qSentId": 11},{"answer": " Have you started planning", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 13, "question": " I know.  I am so excited.  I cant believe its actually happening", "qSentId": 12},{"answer": " A little bit.  We picked a place and a date", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 14, "question": " Have you started planning", "qSentId": 13},{"answer": " Where will it be", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 15, "question": " A little bit.  We picked a place and a date", "qSentId": 14},{"answer": " At my aunts house in the country on June 9th", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 16, "question": " Where will it be", "qSentId": 15},{"answer": "  So youll have an outdoor wedding", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 17, "question": " At my aunts house in the country on June 9th", "qSentId": 16},{"answer": " Yeah", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 18, "question": "  So youll have an outdoor wedding", "qSentId": 17},{"answer": " Have you gotten your dress yet", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 19, "question": " Yeah", "qSentId": 18},{"answer": " Well, Ive picked it out, but I havent gotten it yet", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 20, "question": " Have you gotten your dress yet", "qSentId": 19},{"answer": " Are you still shopping around", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 21, "question": " Well, Ive picked it out, but I havent gotten it yet", "qSentId": 20},{"answer": " No, I definitely want to wear the one I picked out.  But, since the wedding is stil", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 25, "question": " Are you still shopping around", "qSentId": 24},{"answer": " Why", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 29, "question": " No, I definitely want to wear the one I picked out.  But, since the wedding is stil", "qSentId": 28},{"answer": " So I can get in better shape.  I dont want to buy it now and then lose a bunch o", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 30, "question": " Why", "qSentId": 29},{"answer": " You dont need to get in shape.  You look great now", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 34, "question": " So I can get in better shape.  I dont want to buy it now and then lose a bunch o", "qSentId": 33},{"answer": " Oh, thanks for saying that, but I need to get in shape.  My goal is to lose about 2", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 35, "question": " You dont need to get in shape.  You look great now", "qSentId": 34},{"answer": " I guess you want to look as good as possible on your big day", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 39, "question": " Oh, thanks for saying that, but I need to get in shape.  My goal is to lose about 2", "qSentId": 38},{"answer": " Exactly", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 40, "question": " I guess you want to look as good as possible on your big day", "qSentId": 39},{"answer": " So, what are you going to do to get in shape", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 41, "question": " Exactly", "qSentId": 40},{"answer": " Well, Im going to watch what I eat.  Im trying to eat less and to eat more fruit", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 42, "question": " So, what are you going to do to get in shape", "qSentId": 41},{"answer": " That sounds like a good plan", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 46, "question": " Well, Im going to watch what I eat.  Im trying to eat less and to eat more fruit", "qSentId": 45},{"answer": " And I need to start some kind of exercise routine too.  Im not sure what to do", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 47, "question": " That sounds like a good plan", "qSentId": 46},{"answer": " Thanks.  I just try to eat right and do lots of different exercises each week", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 52, "question": " And I need to start some kind of exercise routine too.  Im not sure what to do", "qSentId": 51},{"answer": " Like what", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 53, "question": " Thanks.  I just try to eat right and do lots of different exercises each week", "qSentId": 52},{"answer": " Well, for example, one week I might do something different each day lik", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 54, "question": " Like what", "qSentId": 53},{"answer": " Do you work out each day", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 58, "question": " Well, for example, one week I might do something different each day lik", "qSentId": 57},{"answer": " I try to work out each weekday.  I take a break on the weekend", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 59, "question": " Do you work out each day", "qSentId": 58},{"answer": " What do you think is the best thing to get me in shape quickly for the wedding", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 60, "question": " I try to work out each weekday.  I take a break on the weekend", "qSentId": 59},{"answer": " Well, maybe you should do exercises like walking or yoga twice a week an", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 61, "question": " What do you think is the best thing to get me in shape quickly for the wedding", "qSentId": 60},{"answer": " I really should try that.  I need to get rid of this fat on my arms before th", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 69, "question": " Well, maybe you should do exercises like walking or yoga twice a week an", "qSentId": 68},{"answer": " Lifting weights will really help that.  Youll get toned and strong", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 73, "question": " I really should try that.  I need to get rid of this fat on my arms before th", "qSentId": 72},{"answer": " Five days a week is a lot though.  I dont know if I have time for that", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 74, "question": " Lifting weights will really help that.  Youll get toned and strong", "qSentId": 73},{"answer": " It seems like a lot, but all you really need is a half an hour to an hour each day", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 75, "question": " Five days a week is a lot though.  I dont know if I have time for that", "qSentId": 74},{"answer": " I guess I could do that.  Ill have to try to exercise instead of watching TV", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 79, "question": " It seems like a lot, but all you really need is a half an hour to an hour each day", "qSentId": 78},{"answer": " You know, if you want, we could work out together.  Its always easier if you d", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 80, "question": " I guess I could do that.  Ill have to try to exercise instead of watching TV", "qSentId": 79},{"answer": " Really?  That would be great", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 84, "question": " You know, if you want, we could work out together.  Its always easier if you d", "qSentId": 83},{"answer": " Lets meet at 7:00 each night during the week to exercise", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 85, "question": " Really?  That would be great", "qSentId": 84},{"answer": " Great.  With your help, Ill be in great shape for the wedding", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 86, "question": " Lets meet at 7:00 each night during the week to exercise", "qSentId": 85},{"answer": " I know you will", "docId": "10-10", "aSentId": 87, "question": " Great.  With your help, Ill be in great shape for the wedding", "qSentId": 86}]
